<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".MainActivity">
<androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        tools:ignore="MissingConstraints">


        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/text"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="28dp"
            android:text="A view group that allows the view hierarchy placed within it to be scrolled. Scroll view may have only one direct child placed within it. To add multiple views within the scroll view, make the direct child you add a view group, for example LinearLayout, and place additional views within that LinearLayout.Scroll view supports vertical scrolling only. For horizontal scrolling, use HorizontalScrollView instead.
Never add a RecyclerView or scrolling patterns.Material Design offers guidelines on how
 the appearance of several UI components, The ScrollView is a generic scrollable container, which scrolls multiple child components and views inside it. In the ScrollView, we can scroll the components in both direction vertically and horizontally. By default, the ScrollView container scrolls its components and views in verticalThe ScrollView is a generic scrollable container, which scrolls multiple child components and views inside it. In the ScrollView, we can scroll the components in both direction vertically and horizontally. By default, the ScrollView container scrolls its components and views in verticalThe ScrollView is a generic scrollable container, which scrolls multiple child components and views inside it. In the ScrollView, we can scroll the components in both direction vertically and horizontally. By default, the ScrollView container scrolls its components and views in verticalThe ScrollView is a generic scrollable container, which scrolls multiple child components and views inside it. In the ScrollView, we can scroll the components in both direction vertically and horizontally. By default, the ScrollView container scrolls its components and views in verticalThe ScrollView is a generic scrollable container, which scrolls multiple child components and views inside it. In the ScrollView, we can scroll the components in both direction vertically and horizontally. By default, the ScrollView container scrolls its components and views in verticalThe ScrollView is a generic scrollable container, which scrolls multiple child components and views inside it. In the ScrollView, we can scroll the components in both direction vertically and horizontally. By default, the ScrollView container scrolls its components and views in verticalThe ScrollView is a generic scrollable container, which scrolls multiple child components and views inside it. In the ScrollView, we can scroll the components in both direction vertically and horizontally. By default, the ScrollView container scrolls its components and views in verticalThe ScrollView is a generic scrollable container, which scrolls multiple child components and views inside it. In the ScrollView, we can scroll the components in both direction vertically and horizontally. By default, the ScrollView container scrolls its components and views in verticalThe ScrollView is a generic scrollable container, which scrolls multiple child components and views inside it. In the ScrollView, we can scroll the components in both direction vertically and horizontally. By default, the ScrollView container scrolls its components and views in verticalincluding app bars and banners, should respond to gestures."
            app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
            app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.0"
            app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
            app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />

        <androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="198dp"
            android:layout_marginTop="53dp"

            app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/text"
            tools:layout_editor_absoluteX="0dp">

            <androidx.recyclerview.widget.RecyclerView
                android:id="@+id/appDetails"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginStart="5dp"
                android:layout_marginEnd="5dp"
                android:overScrollMode="never"
                app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.307"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/text" />
        </androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView>
    </androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>

</androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView>




</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>